<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Logistics on BarCamp Cork</title>
    <link>https://barcampcork.org/categories/logistics/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Logistics on BarCamp Cork</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2010 18:25:50 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://barcampcork.org/categories/logistics/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The Parking</title>
      <link>https://barcampcork.org/2010/11/18/the-parking/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2010 18:25:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://barcampcork.org/2010/11/18/the-parking/</guid>
      <description>All day parking is available from Q-Park (across the road from the Barcamp Cork venue) for a special Barcamp Cork rate of 10euro.
All you have to do is get your ticket stamped by us from the event. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Speakers</title>
      <link>https://barcampcork.org/2010/11/18/the-speakers/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2010 08:07:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://barcampcork.org/2010/11/18/the-speakers/</guid>
      <description>If you are a speaker and are wish to be on at a certain time or have a time preference, please email myself about these including the title of your talk: me jameswhelton com
secondly, if you wish to give a talk, but feel you can&amp;rsquo;t fill a session period, why not split the session with someone else? Shoot me an email if this is the case.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Wifi</title>
      <link>https://barcampcork.org/2010/11/17/the-wifi/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2010 13:10:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://barcampcork.org/2010/11/17/the-wifi/</guid>
      <description>To confirm, **yes **there will be free wifi at the event, a password will be given on the day (we don&amp;rsquo;t want you to throttle your data connection just yet).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The (Provisional) Timetable</title>
      <link>https://barcampcork.org/2010/11/11/the-provisional-timetable/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2010 13:42:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://barcampcork.org/2010/11/11/the-provisional-timetable/</guid>
      <description>What excitement, just over a week to Barcamp Cork!
The day will kick off at 10:00am with registration and Coffee from 10:00 to 10:15. The day will end at 5pm with &amp;lsquo;afters&amp;rsquo; to be arranged :)
The talks will be running in 4 separate rooms throughout the day, the Blacknight Room, the Microsoft Room, the JustMobile Room and the Maxroam Room. Each speaker is given 30 minutes (questions included in that time) and 15 minutes for a changeover in between.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Organisers </title>
      <link>https://barcampcork.org/2010/11/10/the-organisers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2010 13:44:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://barcampcork.org/2010/11/10/the-organisers/</guid>
      <description>From left to right: Ciara Feely Cahalane James Whelton Ciara Crossan</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Parking</title>
      <link>https://barcampcork.org/2008/10/31/parking/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2008 09:52:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://barcampcork.org/2008/10/31/parking/</guid>
      <description>There is no parking in the Webworks building. However the City Hall Cark Park is facing the front door right across Eglinton Street. It&amp;rsquo;s a bit pricey but no worse than any of the others from what I can see. Cheapest option is to park in the Railway Station carpark for €6 per day. It&amp;rsquo;s maybe a 10-15 min walk.
Push-pin B below is at entrance to both Webworks and the City Hall Car Park.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BarCamp The Afters</title>
      <link>https://barcampcork.org/2008/10/30/barcamp-the-afters/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2008 15:40:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://barcampcork.org/2008/10/30/barcamp-the-afters/</guid>
      <description>After a bit of tooing and froing, we&amp;rsquo;ve decided to have no official place for food after BarCamp, it&amp;rsquo;s just too awkward to arrange for that many people. There are tons of good places to eat in the city centre and I&amp;rsquo;m sure groups of you can organise yourselves.
However, the final destination of the evening will be The Bierhaus on Pope&amp;rsquo;s Quay. The route is as follows:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BarCamp Cork II is confirmed</title>
      <link>https://barcampcork.org/2008/09/04/hello-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2008 11:25:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://barcampcork.org/2008/09/04/hello-world/</guid>
      <description>We have a date: November 1st 2008
We have a venue: Webworks, Eglinton Street, Cork
We have a blog.
We have 4 weeks.
For the next few days, we&amp;rsquo;ll post some thoughts on some of the things we&amp;rsquo;d like to achieve with this BarCamp. The focus is on trying new ideas and trying to put the Un back in Unconference.
The venue/wireless is being kindly provided by EI/IDA/Howard Holdings. The blog is kindly hosted by Blacknight Solutions.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
