<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Vision on BarCamp Cork</title>
    <link>https://www.barcampcork.org/categories/vision/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Vision on BarCamp Cork</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2010 18:14:02 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.barcampcork.org/categories/vision/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The Call For Volunteers</title>
      <link>https://www.barcampcork.org/2010/11/18/the-call-for-volunteers/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2010 18:14:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.barcampcork.org/2010/11/18/the-call-for-volunteers/</guid>
      <description>If you wish to really be a massive help to Barcamp Cork, find myself, James Whelton, on the morning to find out how you can give a hand or email me: me(@)jameswhelton(.)com
We are looking for people to be ready to pounce on matters such as presentation difficulties, etc, and just to float around willing to give a hand. I&amp;rsquo;m sure there will be enough of you fellow geeks there willing to give a hand with the technical stuff :)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What&#39;s the purpose of this bar camp?</title>
      <link>https://www.barcampcork.org/2008/10/06/whats-the-purpose-of-this-bar-camp/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2008 13:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.barcampcork.org/2008/10/06/whats-the-purpose-of-this-bar-camp/</guid>
      <description>I really hope I make it on the 1st but even if I don&amp;rsquo;t I wanted to make a point that the informal dialogue we are supposed to have as people interested in Web 2.0 is one we should extend to brands and organisations.
I don&amp;rsquo;t mean we should set up Bar Camp to sell services to them but I mean it&amp;rsquo;s be really valuable to engage with the corporate sector and the public sector so we can learn more about where they perceive their problems to be.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BarCamp Cork Manifesto</title>
      <link>https://www.barcampcork.org/2008/09/29/barcamp-cork-manifesto/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2008 19:29:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.barcampcork.org/2008/09/29/barcamp-cork-manifesto/</guid>
      <description>We&amp;rsquo;ve had a lot of great *Camps in Ireland since the first BarCamp Cork back in 2006. We&amp;rsquo;ve learned lots, become friends with many people we&amp;rsquo;ve met there and hopefully shared what knowledge we have.
However one discussion topic that has bubbled up regularly in between the Irish BarCamps has been the very structured format of them. Many feel that we&amp;rsquo;ve perhaps not fully embraced the &amp;ldquo;Un&amp;rdquo; aspect of Unconference. The fear of the unknown and fear of failure would have been my reason for trying to make sure everything was &amp;ldquo;organised&amp;rdquo; in advance of the first BarCamp.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
