<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>cork on BarCamp Cork</title>
    <link>https://barcampcork.org/tags/cork/</link>
    <description>Recent content in cork on BarCamp Cork</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2010 13:42:38 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://barcampcork.org/tags/cork/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The (Provisional) Timetable</title>
      <link>https://barcampcork.org/2010/11/11/the-provisional-timetable/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2010 13:42:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://barcampcork.org/2010/11/11/the-provisional-timetable/</guid>
      <description>What excitement, just over a week to Barcamp Cork!
The day will kick off at 10:00am with registration and Coffee from 10:00 to 10:15. The day will end at 5pm with &amp;lsquo;afters&amp;rsquo; to be arranged :)
The talks will be running in 4 separate rooms throughout the day, the Blacknight Room, the Microsoft Room, the JustMobile Room and the Maxroam Room. Each speaker is given 30 minutes (questions included in that time) and 15 minutes for a changeover in between.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Venue: Webworks Cork</title>
      <link>https://barcampcork.org/2010/10/21/venue-webworks-cork/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Oct 2010 17:34:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://barcampcork.org/2010/10/21/venue-webworks-cork/</guid>
      <description>Image by cwjoneill via Flickr
I am excited to announce that the venue we have chosen for BarCamp Cork IV is the Webworks Cork. The Enterprise Ireland Webworks is a fully serviced office facility in the city centre developed for the benefit of services focussed small and medium enterprises (SMEs) trading internationally from Cork. The facility offers 3,300 square metres of enterprise space broken up into 36 distinct units with a capacity to accommodate up to 450 people.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BarCamp Cork 2010</title>
      <link>https://barcampcork.org/2010/10/14/barcamp-cork-2010/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Oct 2010 16:27:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://barcampcork.org/2010/10/14/barcamp-cork-2010/</guid>
      <description>I am delighted to announce that BarCamp Cork 2010 will take place on the 20th of November this year. Currently the venue is being finalised and we are getting our sponsors in order. I am thrilled that Microsoft Ireland and Maxroam have decided to be sponsors of BarCamp Cork this year.
So ladies and gentle please head over to the Sign-Up/Register page and get registered! We hope to have a massive attendance this year!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BarCamp Cork III is Confirmed</title>
      <link>https://barcampcork.org/2009/09/23/barcamp-cork-iii-is-confirmed/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2009 10:22:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://barcampcork.org/2009/09/23/barcamp-cork-iii-is-confirmed/</guid>
      <description>Planning Barcamp Cork the 3rd is underway!
The venue is Cork International Airport Hotel.
The Date is Saturday November the 14th 2009. (CorkMeet2009 is running the preceeding few days, 11th to 13th)
Watch this space for updates and the @BarCampCork Twitter account too.
Blacknight have covered the cost of hosting this site for another year, Thank you Blacknight.
Meet the organisers of this years Barcamp:
From left to right, Ciara Feely, Gordon Murray and Ciara Crossan.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
