<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Admin on BarCamp Cork</title>
    <link>https://barcampcork.com/categories/admin/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Admin on BarCamp Cork</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2008 11:07:10 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://barcampcork.com/categories/admin/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Kids at BarCamp</title>
      <link>https://barcampcork.com/2008/10/15/kids-at-barcamp/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2008 11:07:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://barcampcork.com/2008/10/15/kids-at-barcamp/</guid>
      <description>We have at least one person coming on November 1st who will have a child in tow. We want to facilitate this in a way that works best for everyone. Would love to get some ideas here. Obviously babies are no problem at all and older ones can take care of themselves but how best to deal with other ages? I&amp;rsquo;m happy to bring game consoles etc and put them somewhere they can hang out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Registration Form is now live</title>
      <link>https://barcampcork.com/2008/09/29/registration-form-is-now-live/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2008 22:42:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://barcampcork.com/2008/09/29/registration-form-is-now-live/</guid>
      <description>Add your details, tell us how you are going to make BarCamp Cork II the best event you&amp;rsquo;ve ever attended and let us know what we can do to make it even better over the next 4 weeks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What we need</title>
      <link>https://barcampcork.com/2008/09/29/what-we-need/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2008 20:30:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://barcampcork.com/2008/09/29/what-we-need/</guid>
      <description>We&amp;rsquo;re aiming for BarCamp-lite this time around. A minimum of fuss and bother around irrelevant contextual stuff and a maximum focus on making a kick-ass day that will be remembered. Having said that, we do need help with a bunch of things. If you can help with these in any way, please contact us at barcampcork AT gmail DOT com:
  Contributors - See the Manifesto post. A sign-up form will go up this week so you can register your interest in attending and giving some indication of how you would like to contribute on the day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BarCamp Cork II is confirmed</title>
      <link>https://barcampcork.com/2008/09/04/hello-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2008 11:25:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://barcampcork.com/2008/09/04/hello-world/</guid>
      <description>We have a date: November 1st 2008
We have a venue: Webworks, Eglinton Street, Cork
We have a blog.
We have 4 weeks.
For the next few days, we&amp;rsquo;ll post some thoughts on some of the things we&amp;rsquo;d like to achieve with this BarCamp. The focus is on trying new ideas and trying to put the Un back in Unconference.
The venue/wireless is being kindly provided by EI/IDA/Howard Holdings. The blog is kindly hosted by Blacknight Solutions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BarCampIreland Backnetwork</title>
      <link>https://barcampcork.com/2006/09/28/barcampireland-backnetwork/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2006 12:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://barcampcork.com/2006/09/28/barcampireland-backnetwork/</guid>
      <description>The backnetwork is filling up nicely with people (don’t forget to make links to those you know) and we are just ready for the day.
If we don’t have your email address then we can’t send an invite.
But we will have a page up on the day with sign-up codes so you can grab one and sign-up via Wifi on the spot or do so after you get home.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Friday Evening</title>
      <link>https://barcampcork.com/2006/09/28/friday-evening/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2006 12:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://barcampcork.com/2006/09/28/friday-evening/</guid>
      <description>For those of you who are around on Friday evening, the un-plan is as follows:
I’ll be in Webworks all day at an EI course and we’ll be getting things like chairs, drinks and AV delivered throughout the day.
That course finishes at 5.30 4ish and we switch into BarCamp mode then. We will be doing setup for however long it takes so please pop on over to lend a hand if you are free.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Volunteers</title>
      <link>https://barcampcork.com/2006/09/28/volunteers/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2006 12:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://barcampcork.com/2006/09/28/volunteers/</guid>
      <description>We have a good bunch of people who have signed up as volunteers for the day. Many thanks to you all. Walter just did a mail-shot to you with a list of the things that need to be handled. The things we will need help with include:
Setup: Chairs and tables and AV stuff.
Rooms: One person per room to make sure everything is going smoothly and also to encourage discussion by asking questions if everyone is shy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Global Connections</title>
      <link>https://barcampcork.com/2006/09/28/global-connections/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2006 10:19:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://barcampcork.com/2006/09/28/global-connections/</guid>
      <description>The guys organising BarCampMilwaukee want to do what they are calling a “Global Connections” session. They realised that their event, BarCampVienna, BarCampBerlin, BarCampIreland and others are all on over the same two day period and thought it might be interesting to hook up by various means at one point on Saturday.
Unfortunately they are running this at 7pm our time at which point we will all be gone. However, I thought it was worth mentioning in case any of our attendees wanted to hook up with these guys on their own to share experiences after our event.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Webworks pictures</title>
      <link>https://barcampcork.com/2006/09/26/webworks-pictures/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2006 08:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://barcampcork.com/2006/09/26/webworks-pictures/</guid>
      <description>I took a few piccies of Webworks yesterday. It’s a lovely building with a great internal layout. Members of the backnetwork will see these automatically appear on the photos page. If you are not a member, that means you have not sent us your e-mail address. So send them on!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Presentation tools</title>
      <link>https://barcampcork.com/2006/09/24/presentation-tools/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2006 10:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://barcampcork.com/2006/09/24/presentation-tools/</guid>
      <description>I guess most people presenting will either
 Just talk Have Powerpoint Slides Have OpenOffice Impress slides Do live demos Give Wink screencasts Mime  Anyone intending to use Eric Meyer’s S5 as demonstrated to great effect by some of the microformats guys?
S5 is a Simple Standards based Slide Show System which uses XHTML, CSS, and JavaScript. If I manage to do a talk I’ll be basing a major part of it on existing S5-based presentations so I guess I’ll end up using it by default.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We need projectors</title>
      <link>https://barcampcork.com/2006/09/24/projecters-now-sorted-thank-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2006 10:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://barcampcork.com/2006/09/24/projecters-now-sorted-thank-you/</guid>
      <description>Big thank you to Michael, Gavin, Christian and Damien for coming up trumps with projectors. This means all the rest of you better be Powerpointing or OpenOffice’ing like the wind this weekend.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We need projectors</title>
      <link>https://barcampcork.com/2006/09/22/we-need-projectors/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2006 11:19:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://barcampcork.com/2006/09/22/we-need-projectors/</guid>
      <description>We’re putting the call out again for projectors. At €125 a pop for the day, we’d prefer to not have to pay for these. At the moment we are assuming three parallel sessions but that may rise. Ideally we’d love to have 4 projectors or more. At the moment we have only one confirmed</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>C&amp;C to provide beverages on the day</title>
      <link>https://barcampcork.com/2006/09/20/cc-to-provide-beverages-on-the-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2006 13:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://barcampcork.com/2006/09/20/cc-to-provide-beverages-on-the-day/</guid>
      <description>The fine people over at C&amp;amp;C Group have agreed to sponsor our event by providing a selection of different soft drinks. This is quite an important one as I’m sure every attendee will be parched from all their speaking. We will only provide drinks to those who sound hoarse Thanks Paula!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blacknight are our latest sponsors</title>
      <link>https://barcampcork.com/2006/09/20/blacknight-are-our-latest-sponsors/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2006 13:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://barcampcork.com/2006/09/20/blacknight-are-our-latest-sponsors/</guid>
      <description>Michele over at Irish web-host provider Blacknight has kindly offered to sponsor some of the after-event celebrations. Now we just need to figure out what those celebrations are. Thanks Michele. We really are getting a lovely mix of sponsors now.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Talk Talk</title>
      <link>https://barcampcork.com/2006/09/20/talk-talk/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2006 09:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://barcampcork.com/2006/09/20/talk-talk/</guid>
      <description>We’re playing with some options for online chat during the event. IRC is the most obvious one but we need to make sure that we have a web interface to that for those who don’t have an IRC client installed. One neat little doodah we found is Lace which is a nice web-based mini-chatroom. The author</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We need your e-mail addresses</title>
      <link>https://barcampcork.com/2006/09/20/we-need-your-e-mail-addresses/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2006 09:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://barcampcork.com/2006/09/20/we-need-your-e-mail-addresses/</guid>
      <description>One thing which we have avoided on the wiki is asking for your e-mail addresses. This is both for privacy and to stop scumbag spammers harvesting them. However, to take part in the backnetwork, we will need to send you an activation code. If you wish to take part (and we recommend you do), please send</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Madgex provides BarCampIreland with a backnetwork</title>
      <link>https://barcampcork.com/2006/09/19/madgex-provides-barcampireland-with-a-backnetwork/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2006 17:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://barcampcork.com/2006/09/19/madgex-provides-barcampireland-with-a-backnetwork/</guid>
      <description>This really is the icing on the cake for the event. Madgex, a web development company based in Brighton, are providing a full backnetwork for BarCampIreland. Have a look at the one they did for the d.Construct 2006 conference recently. Just to list some of the features:
Every attendee gets a profile page You can indicate your</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fear of Flying</title>
      <link>https://barcampcork.com/2006/09/19/fear-of-flying/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2006 09:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://barcampcork.com/2006/09/19/fear-of-flying/</guid>
      <description>Elly has signed up to talk about getting non-technical people using web technologies. This is something I obsess about a lot. We got my Dad from technophobe to e-mail to SMS to RyanAir.com in five short(!) years. Hell he googled for someone yesterday. There is still a long way to go but I’m one of</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Check out the pimped-up logos!</title>
      <link>https://barcampcork.com/2006/09/18/check-out-the-pimped-up-logos/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2006 15:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://barcampcork.com/2006/09/18/check-out-the-pimped-up-logos/</guid>
      <description>We updated the logos on this blog and on the Wiki with the design that is going on the t-shirts. A big thanks again to Ed and Tomasz in Hosting365 for sorting these out for us. Definitely the best variation on the core BarCamp logo I’ve seen so far.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tell us all about yourself</title>
      <link>https://barcampcork.com/2006/09/18/tell-us-all-about-yourself/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2006 12:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://barcampcork.com/2006/09/18/tell-us-all-about-yourself/</guid>
      <description>I’ve just put a Profiles page up on the Wiki. The idea is to provide a very short outline of your background so that people can discover those of similar interests and perhaps come up with some new ideas for presentations that they can give or would like to hear. I saw a joint presentation</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Another excellent sponsor</title>
      <link>https://barcampcork.com/2006/09/18/another-excellent-sponsor/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2006 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://barcampcork.com/2006/09/18/another-excellent-sponsor/</guid>
      <description>We’re delighted to announce that Sigmar Recruitment have decided to sponsor BarCampIreland. Thanks! Every sponsor we get is a great validation of the value of the event. There is now a very strong desire to make this the first of many BarCamps around the country.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fantastic idea for a session</title>
      <link>https://barcampcork.com/2006/09/17/fantastic-idea-for-a-session/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2006 20:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://barcampcork.com/2006/09/17/fantastic-idea-for-a-session/</guid>
      <description>Emmet has come up with an awesome idea for some of the sessions at BarCampIreland. He has mentioned it here and over at the Wiki and is looking for people to sign-up. The concept is called Petcha Kucha (or Klaatu Barada Nikto as I keep saying) and the basic idea is that each speaker presents 20</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>And in the equally long tradition of the hours after an event</title>
      <link>https://barcampcork.com/2006/09/15/and-in-the-equally-long-tradition-of-the-hours-after-an-event/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2006 10:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://barcampcork.com/2006/09/15/and-in-the-equally-long-tradition-of-the-hours-after-an-event/</guid>
      <description>Adam wonders if we should have BeerCamp afterwards. We’ve some ideas there but shout out your suggestions for what and where. For the utterly confused the overall BarCamp blog itself points out that it is “bar” as in foo not Bar as in Beer. I think we should do a quick test at the door to</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>In the long tradition of the night before</title>
      <link>https://barcampcork.com/2006/09/14/in-the-long-tradition-of-the-night-before/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2006 13:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://barcampcork.com/2006/09/14/in-the-long-tradition-of-the-night-before/</guid>
      <description>Joe Drumgoole wonders if anyone is around on the Friday night before the BarCamp starts. Damien, Walter and I will be in town getting the place set up so I think he can count on all of us being up for something. Walter has suggested Wagamama to start with and I second that since I’ve been</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to monitor the blog buzz on BarCampIreland</title>
      <link>https://barcampcork.com/2006/09/13/how-to-monitor-the-blog-buzz-on-barcampireland/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2006 14:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://barcampcork.com/2006/09/13/how-to-monitor-the-blog-buzz-on-barcampireland/</guid>
      <description>First off, if you do blog about the event, please please add BarCampIreland as a Technorati tag. Then as Walter pointed out to me, anyone can subscribe to the RSS feed for that term or you can just keep an eye on this page over at Technorati to catch all the buzz in one place.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>T-shirts coming along nicely</title>
      <link>https://barcampcork.com/2006/09/13/t-shirts-coming-along-nicely/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2006 06:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://barcampcork.com/2006/09/13/t-shirts-coming-along-nicely/</guid>
      <description>We are deeply grateful for all sponsorship of the event but we’d particularly like to highlight the work being done by Ed Byrne and Tomasz of hosting365. They have been unreasonably patient with us as we tried to figure out exactly what logo we wanted. Tomasz put together a bunch of great options in double</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>More sponsors</title>
      <link>https://barcampcork.com/2006/09/12/more-sponsors/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2006 08:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://barcampcork.com/2006/09/12/more-sponsors/</guid>
      <description>Trinity Venture Capital have kindly given us sponsorship and will be speaking at the event too. We’re guessing a talk entitled “Understanding and accessing venture capital funding” is going to be ever so slightly popular.
We hopefully be announcing another sponsor or two over the next couple of days.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sponsors</title>
      <link>https://barcampcork.com/2006/09/10/sponsors/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Sep 2006 09:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://barcampcork.com/2006/09/10/sponsors/</guid>
      <description>We’d like to thank all of our confirmed sponsors so far:
 Webworks (and Enterprise Ireland) for the great building and free WiFi Heineken Ireland Qumas Roam4Free Bubble Brothers Hosting365  If you wish to sponsor the event in any way please contact Conor O’Neill, Walter Higgins or Damien Mulley.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
