<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>unconference on BarCamp Cork</title>
    <link>https://barcampcork.org/tags/unconference/</link>
    <description>Recent content in unconference on BarCamp Cork</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2008 10:23:46 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://barcampcork.org/tags/unconference/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Organising a *Camp</title>
      <link>https://barcampcork.org/2008/11/09/organising-a-camp/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2008 10:23:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://barcampcork.org/2008/11/09/organising-a-camp/</guid>
      <description>If you attended BarCamp Cork and thought you&amp;rsquo;d like to run an unconference yourself, below is just a quick idea of what is involved.
  Try to have 2 and preferably 3 organisers. It&amp;rsquo;s possible as a solo run but can add to your stress level.
  The venue is the number 1 priority. If you can get it for free then you&amp;rsquo;ve done 75% of the work already.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Session Topics,Timing and You</title>
      <link>https://barcampcork.org/2008/10/20/session-topicstiming-and-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2008 00:02:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://barcampcork.org/2008/10/20/session-topicstiming-and-you/</guid>
      <description>We&amp;rsquo;ll be posting a page later today with all of the session topics suggested so far by people. However there is one aspect which we need to make clear. BarCamp is a non-commercial unconference and, as such, straight company or product pitches are not appropriate.
We don&amp;rsquo;t want to sound negative about this but it&amp;rsquo;s important. We all love our own companies and our own apps but speaking for 20 minutes about you isn&amp;rsquo;t really that interesting or educational.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kids at BarCamp</title>
      <link>https://barcampcork.org/2008/10/15/kids-at-barcamp/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2008 11:07:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://barcampcork.org/2008/10/15/kids-at-barcamp/</guid>
      <description>We have at least one person coming on November 1st who will have a child in tow. We want to facilitate this in a way that works best for everyone. Would love to get some ideas here. Obviously babies are no problem at all and older ones can take care of themselves but how best to deal with other ages? I&amp;rsquo;m happy to bring game consoles etc and put them somewhere they can hang out.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
