<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Sponsors on BarCamp Cork</title>
    <link>https://barcampcork.org/categories/sponsors/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Sponsors on BarCamp Cork</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 Nov 2010 10:24:11 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://barcampcork.org/categories/sponsors/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The Competitions</title>
      <link>https://barcampcork.org/2010/11/19/the-competitions/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Nov 2010 10:24:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://barcampcork.org/2010/11/19/the-competitions/</guid>
      <description>Barcamp Cork is running 4 competitions on the day, these are being sponsored byDot-Cotton of French Church street, Ellislab and BrokenScreen.ie, with some fantastic prizes, that you wont want to miss out on!
Competiton details will be posted on website on the day (no head-starts :P ) and also on a whiteboard at the event.
Dot-Cotton is Ireland&amp;rsquo;s first and only custom digital print clothes shop, at 14 French Church Street.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Parking</title>
      <link>https://barcampcork.org/2010/11/18/the-parking/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2010 18:25:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://barcampcork.org/2010/11/18/the-parking/</guid>
      <description>All day parking is available from Q-Park (across the road from the Barcamp Cork venue) for a special Barcamp Cork rate of 10euro.
All you have to do is get your ticket stamped by us from the event. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Sponsors</title>
      <link>https://barcampcork.org/2010/11/10/the-sponsors/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2010 13:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://barcampcork.org/2010/11/10/the-sponsors/</guid>
      <description>An event like Barcamp Cork or any other event for that matter could not run without sponsors. This year we have some fantastic sponsors that have been absolutely amazing to us, helping us organise a free conference for you! Reciprocate the kindness and check them out!
Microsoft Ireland
Blacknight
   Just Mobile
   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Competition suggestions</title>
      <link>https://barcampcork.org/2009/11/26/competition-suggestions/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Nov 2009 12:32:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://barcampcork.org/2009/11/26/competition-suggestions/</guid>
      <description>Thanks to the Sponsors of Barcamp Cork 2009, Microsoft, Assembly Point, Reilly &amp;amp; Co and Nitrosell, we have some freebies what we&amp;rsquo;d like to give away.
We&amp;rsquo;d like to run a fun competition which a few people can win, we&amp;rsquo;ll be giving away some great free techie stuff. We&amp;rsquo;d like if the competition promoted the sponsors too since they helped make Barcamp happen.
Any fun ideas for a competition?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hotel Discounts</title>
      <link>https://barcampcork.org/2008/10/23/hotel-discounts/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2008 15:07:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://barcampcork.org/2008/10/23/hotel-discounts/</guid>
      <description>The cool guys at Roomex.com have just become our latest sponsors by giving us a bunch of discounts for Cork hotels in their system. Keep a close eye over the next 24hrs as they mentioned there will be more discounts by tomorrow.

I see 15 Cork hotels listed on our special BarCamp page with a wide variety of prices. The eagle-eyed amongst you will notice that actually all of their 20,000 hotels have an extra BarCamp discount on them so you have a week to book all of your upcoming travel!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Two more Sponsors</title>
      <link>https://barcampcork.org/2008/10/23/two-more-sponsors/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2008 10:12:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://barcampcork.org/2008/10/23/two-more-sponsors/</guid>
      <description>A big thank you to Pat Phelan of Cubic Telecom for sponsoring the lunch at BarCamp. The ice-swans and champagne fountains have been ordered. But seriously, Pat has been a fantastic supporter of of the tech community and many of us are in his debt.

Thanks also to John Henry Donovan of 5pieces who took care of the licensing of our sign-up form. This was totally unexpected and very much appreciated.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Automattic is our latest sponsor</title>
      <link>https://barcampcork.org/2008/09/30/automattic-is-our-latest-sponsor/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2008 19:18:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://barcampcork.org/2008/09/30/automattic-is-our-latest-sponsor/</guid>
      <description>We&amp;rsquo;re genuinely blown away that Donncha, Toni, Matt and the guys n gals in Automattic are sponsoring BarCamp Cork II. You&amp;rsquo;ll probably know them better as the people behind Wordpress, Wordpress.com, Wordpress MU and Akismet.
This blog and thousands of other Irish ones, run on the software created by these guys and are protected from spam by them too. It all runs like a charm on a Blacknight shared hosting account.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Your lunchtime refreshment</title>
      <link>https://barcampcork.org/2006/09/26/your-lunchtime-refreshment/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2006 07:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://barcampcork.org/2006/09/26/your-lunchtime-refreshment/</guid>
      <description>Courtesy of Bubble Brothers and La Fortuna wine. I see a bottle of Sauvignon Blanc with my name written all over it.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
