<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>barcampcork on BarCamp Cork</title>
    <link>https://www.barcampcork.org/tags/barcampcork/</link>
    <description>Recent content in barcampcork on BarCamp Cork</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 21 Oct 2010 17:34:11 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.barcampcork.org/tags/barcampcork/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Venue: Webworks Cork</title>
      <link>https://www.barcampcork.org/2010/10/21/venue-webworks-cork/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Oct 2010 17:34:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.barcampcork.org/2010/10/21/venue-webworks-cork/</guid>
      <description>Image by cwjoneill via Flickr
I am excited to announce that the venue we have chosen for BarCamp Cork IV is the Webworks Cork. The Enterprise Ireland Webworks is a fully serviced office facility in the city centre developed for the benefit of services focussed small and medium enterprises (SMEs) trading internationally from Cork. The facility offers 3,300 square metres of enterprise space broken up into 36 distinct units with a capacity to accommodate up to 450 people.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BarCamp Cork 2010</title>
      <link>https://www.barcampcork.org/2010/10/14/barcamp-cork-2010/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Oct 2010 16:27:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.barcampcork.org/2010/10/14/barcamp-cork-2010/</guid>
      <description>I am delighted to announce that BarCamp Cork 2010 will take place on the 20th of November this year. Currently the venue is being finalised and we are getting our sponsors in order. I am thrilled that Microsoft Ireland and Maxroam have decided to be sponsors of BarCamp Cork this year.
So ladies and gentle please head over to the Sign-Up/Register page and get registered! We hope to have a massive attendance this year!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Organising a *Camp</title>
      <link>https://www.barcampcork.org/2008/11/09/organising-a-camp/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2008 10:23:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.barcampcork.org/2008/11/09/organising-a-camp/</guid>
      <description>If you attended BarCamp Cork and thought you&amp;rsquo;d like to run an unconference yourself, below is just a quick idea of what is involved.
  Try to have 2 and preferably 3 organisers. It&amp;rsquo;s possible as a solo run but can add to your stress level.
  The venue is the number 1 priority. If you can get it for free then you&amp;rsquo;ve done 75% of the work already.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The good, the bad and the ugly</title>
      <link>https://www.barcampcork.org/2008/11/09/the-good-the-bad-and-the-ugly/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2008 09:42:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.barcampcork.org/2008/11/09/the-good-the-bad-and-the-ugly/</guid>
      <description>Every BarCamp is different and I hope we can learn each time from what went well and what didn&amp;rsquo;t. I&amp;rsquo;m going to kick off with a few of my thoughts about last weekend but I&amp;rsquo;m much more interested in hearing all of your thoughts.
So in no particular order:
 The venue - still amazing and just ideal for an event like this Rooms - two is not enough. Even the addition of the small third room was insufficient.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thank YOU</title>
      <link>https://www.barcampcork.org/2008/11/09/thank-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2008 09:07:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.barcampcork.org/2008/11/09/thank-you/</guid>
      <description>This post should have been written last weekend so apologies for the slowness.
There are a bunch of people to thank for the success of BarCamp. It genuinely couldn&amp;rsquo;t have happened without them.
 YOU! BarCamp is about everyone contributing in some way. The speakers did an awesome job and everyone else asked, discussed, argued and queried brilliantly. Thank you all (110+ of you) for coming and making it the best BarCamp yet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Carbon Calculator</title>
      <link>https://www.barcampcork.org/2008/11/04/the-carbon-calculator/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2008 16:32:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.barcampcork.org/2008/11/04/the-carbon-calculator/</guid>
      <description>Bart has made the code-drop from Saturday available. He&amp;rsquo;ll do another drop later this week with a better landing page etc.
 It requires:
 Python 2.5 Django 1.0 sqlite3 pysqlite3  Right now you can either access the http://localhost:8000/events/ or the http://localhost:8000/admin/ pages to play around. login: admin pass: barcamp
Code archive file: green.zip</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BarCamp Photos</title>
      <link>https://www.barcampcork.org/2008/11/04/barcamp-photos/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2008 16:28:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.barcampcork.org/2008/11/04/barcamp-photos/</guid>
      <description>You&amp;rsquo;ll find photos of the day in two main locations:
Pix.ie Flickr
Some of the snappers include:
Phil O&amp;rsquo;Kane Alexia Golez Donncha O&amp;rsquo;Caoimh Jessica Mannering Me
In general if you are uploading pics, please tag them with &amp;ldquo;barcampcork&amp;rdquo; so we can find them on the various sites.
Leave a comment below with a direct link to your pics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lost n Found</title>
      <link>https://www.barcampcork.org/2008/11/02/lost-n-found/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Nov 2008 11:16:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.barcampcork.org/2008/11/02/lost-n-found/</guid>
      <description>Several members of an obscure Californian cult with a svengali known only as Black Turtleneck left some of their magic charms behind at BarCamp yesterday. If they are yours, just email me directly on conor AT loudervoice DOT com.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Faces of BarCamp Cork</title>
      <link>https://www.barcampcork.org/2008/11/02/the-faces-of-barcamp-cork/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Nov 2008 10:22:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.barcampcork.org/2008/11/02/the-faces-of-barcamp-cork/</guid>
      <description>This is just brilliant. Well done Ian. Belly laugh on a Sunday morning post-BarCamp

Faces of Barcamp from Ian O&amp;rsquo;Donnell on Vimeo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Post BarCamp Head Clearing</title>
      <link>https://www.barcampcork.org/2008/10/31/post-barcamp-head-clearing/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2008 18:22:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.barcampcork.org/2008/10/31/post-barcamp-head-clearing/</guid>
      <description>Clodagh Kelly is going surfing on Sunday morning. Chat to her at BarCamp if you are interested in taking part. It looks like it&amp;rsquo;ll be at Garrettstown.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BarCamp The Afters</title>
      <link>https://www.barcampcork.org/2008/10/30/barcamp-the-afters/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2008 15:40:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.barcampcork.org/2008/10/30/barcamp-the-afters/</guid>
      <description>After a bit of tooing and froing, we&amp;rsquo;ve decided to have no official place for food after BarCamp, it&amp;rsquo;s just too awkward to arrange for that many people. There are tons of good places to eat in the city centre and I&amp;rsquo;m sure groups of you can organise yourselves.
However, the final destination of the evening will be The Bierhaus on Pope&amp;rsquo;s Quay. The route is as follows:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hotel Discounts</title>
      <link>https://www.barcampcork.org/2008/10/23/hotel-discounts/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2008 15:07:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.barcampcork.org/2008/10/23/hotel-discounts/</guid>
      <description>The cool guys at Roomex.com have just become our latest sponsors by giving us a bunch of discounts for Cork hotels in their system. Keep a close eye over the next 24hrs as they mentioned there will be more discounts by tomorrow.

I see 15 Cork hotels listed on our special BarCamp page with a wide variety of prices. The eagle-eyed amongst you will notice that actually all of their 20,000 hotels have an extra BarCamp discount on them so you have a week to book all of your upcoming travel!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>&#34;Build A Web-App in a Day&#34; at BarCamp</title>
      <link>https://www.barcampcork.org/2008/10/23/build-a-web-app-in-a-day-at-barcamp/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2008 08:52:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.barcampcork.org/2008/10/23/build-a-web-app-in-a-day-at-barcamp/</guid>
      <description>A few of us have been bouncing around the idea of building a web application in one day for the past few months. BarCamp seems like the ideal opportunity to try this. From the sign-up comments, it looks like plenty of people are interested in taking part. Unlike the impromptu style of the rest of the day, this one does require quite a bit of up-front preparation if it is to succeed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>&#34;Learning Django&#34; Tutorial Session</title>
      <link>https://www.barcampcork.org/2008/10/23/learning-django-tutorial-session/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2008 08:35:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.barcampcork.org/2008/10/23/learning-django-tutorial-session/</guid>
      <description>Bartosz Ptaszynski will be running a tutorial session on the Python Web Framework Django. It is aimed at anyone who wants to get a feel for what these frameworks are all about and how they can help you. One group in particular who might benefit are web designers who want some insight into the development process.
Django has effectively become the de facto Python Web framework over the past twelve months.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Talks/Sessions Page now up</title>
      <link>https://www.barcampcork.org/2008/10/21/talkssessions-page-now-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2008 19:56:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.barcampcork.org/2008/10/21/talkssessions-page-now-up/</guid>
      <description>We&amp;rsquo;ve collected all the session/talk ideas received so far and put them on their own page. A lot of people have indicated during sign-up that they want to talk but haven&amp;rsquo;t given a topic yet. We&amp;rsquo;ll update the page as we receive the details from them.
We&amp;rsquo;ll have separate more detailed posts on a couple of the tutorial sessions in the next 2-3 days. The &amp;ldquo;build a web-app in a day&amp;rdquo; post is almost ready.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Session Topics,Timing and You</title>
      <link>https://www.barcampcork.org/2008/10/20/session-topicstiming-and-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2008 00:02:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.barcampcork.org/2008/10/20/session-topicstiming-and-you/</guid>
      <description>We&amp;rsquo;ll be posting a page later today with all of the session topics suggested so far by people. However there is one aspect which we need to make clear. BarCamp is a non-commercial unconference and, as such, straight company or product pitches are not appropriate.
We don&amp;rsquo;t want to sound negative about this but it&amp;rsquo;s important. We all love our own companies and our own apps but speaking for 20 minutes about you isn&amp;rsquo;t really that interesting or educational.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Do You Use Twitter?</title>
      <link>https://www.barcampcork.org/2008/10/19/how-do-you-use-twitter/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2008 22:07:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.barcampcork.org/2008/10/19/how-do-you-use-twitter/</guid>
      <description>Will Knott is doing a session on Twitter at BarCamp.
To help with this, he&amp;rsquo;d really appreciate it if you could fill out a very simple 4 question survey.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Post-BarCamp Food n Drinks</title>
      <link>https://www.barcampcork.org/2008/10/18/post-barcamp-food-n-drinks/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2008 19:29:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.barcampcork.org/2008/10/18/post-barcamp-food-n-drinks/</guid>
      <description>Rather than have everyone scatter to the four winds after BarCamp we&amp;rsquo;ve decided to have a sit-down meal followed by some drinks. I&amp;rsquo;ve heard many good things about the Eastern Tandoori over the years so I&amp;rsquo;d like to suggest that. Please let us know in the comments if you&amp;rsquo;d like to attend. Once we know numbers we should be able to get a good-value fixed price menu.
As for drinks, suggestions?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pre-BarCamp Dinner</title>
      <link>https://www.barcampcork.org/2008/10/17/pre-barcamp-dinner/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2008 23:03:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.barcampcork.org/2008/10/17/pre-barcamp-dinner/</guid>
      <description>Pat Phelan and Alexia Golez are organizing a pre-Barcamp Cork dinner and they would love you to come along. It&amp;rsquo;s on in Bangkok93 (A Taste Of Thailand) on Friday 31st of October at 8pm.
Numbers are limited to 25 so please leave your name over in his blog comments to confirm you are coming. Budget for around €25 a head.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kids at BarCamp</title>
      <link>https://www.barcampcork.org/2008/10/15/kids-at-barcamp/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2008 11:07:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.barcampcork.org/2008/10/15/kids-at-barcamp/</guid>
      <description>We have at least one person coming on November 1st who will have a child in tow. We want to facilitate this in a way that works best for everyone. Would love to get some ideas here. Obviously babies are no problem at all and older ones can take care of themselves but how best to deal with other ages? I&amp;rsquo;m happy to bring game consoles etc and put them somewhere they can hang out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BarCamp Cork II Session Ideas</title>
      <link>https://www.barcampcork.org/2008/10/04/barcamp-cork-ii-session-ideas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2008 10:49:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.barcampcork.org/2008/10/04/barcamp-cork-ii-session-ideas/</guid>
      <description>In keeping with our approach of avoiding too much pre-structuring of the day, we are not going to ask people to formally announce session titles etc. However we do want to get some idea of the areas people want to [a] hear about and [b] talk about. If the day works well, those two things will merge. Rest assured that if you want to talk on something, you will get the opportunity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Check out the awesome BarCamp logo</title>
      <link>https://www.barcampcork.org/2008/10/04/check-out-the-awesome-barcamp-logo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2008 09:58:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.barcampcork.org/2008/10/04/check-out-the-awesome-barcamp-logo/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m not exaggerating when I say I think it&amp;rsquo;s the best BarCamp logo I&amp;rsquo;ve ever seen! John Henry Donovan has done a perfect mash-up of the classic logo with the outline of Cork. Thanks John Henry, looking forward to meeting you in Cork.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Irish Webmaster Forum Meetup before BarCamp</title>
      <link>https://www.barcampcork.org/2008/10/01/irish-webmaster-forum-meetup-before-barcamp/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2008 12:43:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.barcampcork.org/2008/10/01/irish-webmaster-forum-meetup-before-barcamp/</guid>
      <description>The Irish Webmaster Forum is having a social meetup in Cork the night before BarCamp. If you are local or you are coming down on Friday evening, you&amp;rsquo;ll be guaranteed an interesting and fun night. All details over on the discussion board.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Automattic is our latest sponsor</title>
      <link>https://www.barcampcork.org/2008/09/30/automattic-is-our-latest-sponsor/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2008 19:18:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.barcampcork.org/2008/09/30/automattic-is-our-latest-sponsor/</guid>
      <description>We&amp;rsquo;re genuinely blown away that Donncha, Toni, Matt and the guys n gals in Automattic are sponsoring BarCamp Cork II. You&amp;rsquo;ll probably know them better as the people behind Wordpress, Wordpress.com, Wordpress MU and Akismet.
This blog and thousands of other Irish ones, run on the software created by these guys and are protected from spam by them too. It all runs like a charm on a Blacknight shared hosting account.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Registration Form is now live</title>
      <link>https://www.barcampcork.org/2008/09/29/registration-form-is-now-live/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2008 22:42:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.barcampcork.org/2008/09/29/registration-form-is-now-live/</guid>
      <description>Add your details, tell us how you are going to make BarCamp Cork II the best event you&amp;rsquo;ve ever attended and let us know what we can do to make it even better over the next 4 weeks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What we need</title>
      <link>https://www.barcampcork.org/2008/09/29/what-we-need/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2008 20:30:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.barcampcork.org/2008/09/29/what-we-need/</guid>
      <description>We&amp;rsquo;re aiming for BarCamp-lite this time around. A minimum of fuss and bother around irrelevant contextual stuff and a maximum focus on making a kick-ass day that will be remembered. Having said that, we do need help with a bunch of things. If you can help with these in any way, please contact us at barcampcork AT gmail DOT com:
  Contributors - See the Manifesto post. A sign-up form will go up this week so you can register your interest in attending and giving some indication of how you would like to contribute on the day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BarCamp Cork Manifesto</title>
      <link>https://www.barcampcork.org/2008/09/29/barcamp-cork-manifesto/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2008 19:29:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.barcampcork.org/2008/09/29/barcamp-cork-manifesto/</guid>
      <description>We&amp;rsquo;ve had a lot of great *Camps in Ireland since the first BarCamp Cork back in 2006. We&amp;rsquo;ve learned lots, become friends with many people we&amp;rsquo;ve met there and hopefully shared what knowledge we have.
However one discussion topic that has bubbled up regularly in between the Irish BarCamps has been the very structured format of them. Many feel that we&amp;rsquo;ve perhaps not fully embraced the &amp;ldquo;Un&amp;rdquo; aspect of Unconference. The fear of the unknown and fear of failure would have been my reason for trying to make sure everything was &amp;ldquo;organised&amp;rdquo; in advance of the first BarCamp.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BarCamp Cork II is confirmed</title>
      <link>https://www.barcampcork.org/2008/09/04/hello-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2008 11:25:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.barcampcork.org/2008/09/04/hello-world/</guid>
      <description>We have a date: November 1st 2008
We have a venue: Webworks, Eglinton Street, Cork
We have a blog.
We have 4 weeks.
For the next few days, we&amp;rsquo;ll post some thoughts on some of the things we&amp;rsquo;d like to achieve with this BarCamp. The focus is on trying new ideas and trying to put the Un back in Unconference.
The venue/wireless is being kindly provided by EI/IDA/Howard Holdings. The blog is kindly hosted by Blacknight Solutions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact Numbers for all the speakers?</title>
      <link>https://www.barcampcork.org/2006/10/05/contact-numbers-for-all-the-speakers/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2006 08:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.barcampcork.org/2006/10/05/contact-numbers-for-all-the-speakers/</guid>
      <description>Bernie and his gang at IT Tipperary are looking to do interviews with some of the BarCamp speakers. I guess they will be released as podcasts. If you are up for it, send your telephone numbers, Skype details or SIP details to barcampireland at gmail dot com and they’ll make ya famous. Alternatively post them here as comments if you are really brave.
Also, keep adding or sending your PPTs, we only have a tiny collection so far.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tom Morris does OPML for BarCamp</title>
      <link>https://www.barcampcork.org/2006/10/03/tom-morris-does-opml-for-barcamp/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Oct 2006 13:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.barcampcork.org/2006/10/03/tom-morris-does-opml-for-barcamp/</guid>
      <description>Tom Morris gave a talk at BarCamp which, like an idiot, I missed. Luckily he gave me the compact 2 minute version afterwards. He has a nice OPML file of various bits and pieces from the day. Check it out over at his blog.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mark Twomey Video</title>
      <link>https://www.barcampcork.org/2006/10/02/mark-twomey-video/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2006 14:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.barcampcork.org/2006/10/02/mark-twomey-video/</guid>
      <description>It is a little rough looking and the sound is awful, but what can you expect from a CameraPhone?
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Presentations Page now up on wiki</title>
      <link>https://www.barcampcork.org/2006/10/02/presentations-page-now-up-on-wiki/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2006 12:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.barcampcork.org/2006/10/02/presentations-page-now-up-on-wiki/</guid>
      <description>We’ve kicked off a page with the day’s presentations over on the wiki. You can either send the PPTs to us and we’ll upload them for you or you can do it yourself if you wish. Any problems, let us know. I’ll try and list all the talks in any case later today.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Speakers and PPTs</title>
      <link>https://www.barcampcork.org/2006/10/02/speakers-and-ppts/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2006 11:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.barcampcork.org/2006/10/02/speakers-and-ppts/</guid>
      <description>If you gave a talk with slides on Saturday and you are OK with that PPT/ODT being re-distributed, please send them on to barcampireland at gmail dot com and we’ll collect them all together on one page for people to find. Thanks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We’ve been TechCrunched!</title>
      <link>https://www.barcampcork.org/2006/10/02/weve-been-techcrunched/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2006 09:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.barcampcork.org/2006/10/02/weve-been-techcrunched/</guid>
      <description>Sam Sethi over at TechCrunch UK has written about Saturday’s event. For those of you who don’t work in the web area, TechCrunch is the most highly trafficked and highly regarded web 2.0 news site. Sam recently launched the UK arm of it and has been very generous in his coverage of Ireland. Thanks for the mention Sam, I can’t wait to see where the next event will be held over here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pictures and Movies</title>
      <link>https://www.barcampcork.org/2006/10/01/pictures-and-movies/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2006 09:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.barcampcork.org/2006/10/01/pictures-and-movies/</guid>
      <description>We already have a bunch of pictures of the day over at Flickr. If you are uploading, please use barcamp and barcampireland as your tags. If you have pictures and don’t have a Flickr account, send them to us at barcampireland at gmail dot come and we’ll do it for you.
If you go to the Backnetwork, you can see all the pictures and blog posts of the day by those who signed up to the backnetwork.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What a day!</title>
      <link>https://www.barcampcork.org/2006/10/01/what-a-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2006 08:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.barcampcork.org/2006/10/01/what-a-day/</guid>
      <description>I may be one of the organisers but can I just say:
BarCamp Ireland ROCKED!
It was the best event I’ve attended in a very long time and that was entirely due to the enthusiasm of all the attendees and in particular, those who spoke. I’ll do some more posts later but just to say well done</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>8 hours and counting</title>
      <link>https://www.barcampcork.org/2006/09/30/8-hours-and-counting/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2006 01:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.barcampcork.org/2006/09/30/8-hours-and-counting/</guid>
      <description>Webworks is looking great and everything is in place for a really memorable day.
Here’s to an awesome day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BarCampIreland Backnetwork</title>
      <link>https://www.barcampcork.org/2006/09/28/barcampireland-backnetwork/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2006 12:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.barcampcork.org/2006/09/28/barcampireland-backnetwork/</guid>
      <description>The backnetwork is filling up nicely with people (don’t forget to make links to those you know) and we are just ready for the day.
If we don’t have your email address then we can’t send an invite.
But we will have a page up on the day with sign-up codes so you can grab one and sign-up via Wifi on the spot or do so after you get home.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Friday Evening</title>
      <link>https://www.barcampcork.org/2006/09/28/friday-evening/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2006 12:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.barcampcork.org/2006/09/28/friday-evening/</guid>
      <description>For those of you who are around on Friday evening, the un-plan is as follows:
I’ll be in Webworks all day at an EI course and we’ll be getting things like chairs, drinks and AV delivered throughout the day.
That course finishes at 5.30 4ish and we switch into BarCamp mode then. We will be doing setup for however long it takes so please pop on over to lend a hand if you are free.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Volunteers</title>
      <link>https://www.barcampcork.org/2006/09/28/volunteers/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2006 12:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.barcampcork.org/2006/09/28/volunteers/</guid>
      <description>We have a good bunch of people who have signed up as volunteers for the day. Many thanks to you all. Walter just did a mail-shot to you with a list of the things that need to be handled. The things we will need help with include:
Setup: Chairs and tables and AV stuff.
Rooms: One person per room to make sure everything is going smoothly and also to encourage discussion by asking questions if everyone is shy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Global Connections</title>
      <link>https://www.barcampcork.org/2006/09/28/global-connections/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2006 10:19:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.barcampcork.org/2006/09/28/global-connections/</guid>
      <description>The guys organising BarCampMilwaukee want to do what they are calling a “Global Connections” session. They realised that their event, BarCampVienna, BarCampBerlin, BarCampIreland and others are all on over the same two day period and thought it might be interesting to hook up by various means at one point on Saturday.
Unfortunately they are running this at 7pm our time at which point we will all be gone. However, I thought it was worth mentioning in case any of our attendees wanted to hook up with these guys on their own to share experiences after our event.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BarCampIreland Logo on front page of boards.ie</title>
      <link>https://www.barcampcork.org/2006/09/26/barcampireland-logo-on-front-page-of-boardsie/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2006 11:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.barcampcork.org/2006/09/26/barcampireland-logo-on-front-page-of-boardsie/</guid>
      <description>Thanks guys, appreciate the plug!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blog like the wind</title>
      <link>https://www.barcampcork.org/2006/09/26/blog-like-the-wind/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2006 08:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.barcampcork.org/2006/09/26/blog-like-the-wind/</guid>
      <description>We are down to the last few days so I encourage any attendees with blogs to blog the living daylights out of the event in the run-up. Thoughts, concerns, questions, ideas, musings. Bring it on. And don’t forget to tag with BarCampIreland.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Webworks pictures</title>
      <link>https://www.barcampcork.org/2006/09/26/webworks-pictures/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2006 08:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.barcampcork.org/2006/09/26/webworks-pictures/</guid>
      <description>I took a few piccies of Webworks yesterday. It’s a lovely building with a great internal layout. Members of the backnetwork will see these automatically appear on the photos page. If you are not a member, that means you have not sent us your e-mail address. So send them on!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Your lunchtime refreshment</title>
      <link>https://www.barcampcork.org/2006/09/26/your-lunchtime-refreshment/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2006 07:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.barcampcork.org/2006/09/26/your-lunchtime-refreshment/</guid>
      <description>Courtesy of Bubble Brothers and La Fortuna wine. I see a bottle of Sauvignon Blanc with my name written all over it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Anyone want to talk about getting things done GTD?</title>
      <link>https://www.barcampcork.org/2006/09/25/anyone-want-to-talk-about-getting-things-done-gtd/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2006 11:25:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.barcampcork.org/2006/09/25/anyone-want-to-talk-about-getting-things-done-gtd/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m willing to bet that there are a ton of GTD fans in our list of attendees. Anyone willing to give a talk introducing the idea and presenting some practical things that people can start doing immediately?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Presentation tools</title>
      <link>https://www.barcampcork.org/2006/09/24/presentation-tools/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2006 10:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.barcampcork.org/2006/09/24/presentation-tools/</guid>
      <description>I guess most people presenting will either
 Just talk Have Powerpoint Slides Have OpenOffice Impress slides Do live demos Give Wink screencasts Mime  Anyone intending to use Eric Meyer’s S5 as demonstrated to great effect by some of the microformats guys?
S5 is a Simple Standards based Slide Show System which uses XHTML, CSS, and JavaScript. If I manage to do a talk I’ll be basing a major part of it on existing S5-based presentations so I guess I’ll end up using it by default.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We need projectors</title>
      <link>https://www.barcampcork.org/2006/09/24/projecters-now-sorted-thank-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2006 10:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.barcampcork.org/2006/09/24/projecters-now-sorted-thank-you/</guid>
      <description>Big thank you to Michael, Gavin, Christian and Damien for coming up trumps with projectors. This means all the rest of you better be Powerpointing or OpenOffice’ing like the wind this weekend.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We need projectors</title>
      <link>https://www.barcampcork.org/2006/09/22/we-need-projectors/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2006 11:19:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.barcampcork.org/2006/09/22/we-need-projectors/</guid>
      <description>We’re putting the call out again for projectors. At €125 a pop for the day, we’d prefer to not have to pay for these. At the moment we are assuming three parallel sessions but that may rise. Ideally we’d love to have 4 projectors or more. At the moment we have only one confirmed</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>C&amp;C to provide beverages on the day</title>
      <link>https://www.barcampcork.org/2006/09/20/cc-to-provide-beverages-on-the-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2006 13:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.barcampcork.org/2006/09/20/cc-to-provide-beverages-on-the-day/</guid>
      <description>The fine people over at C&amp;amp;C Group have agreed to sponsor our event by providing a selection of different soft drinks. This is quite an important one as I’m sure every attendee will be parched from all their speaking. We will only provide drinks to those who sound hoarse Thanks Paula!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blacknight are our latest sponsors</title>
      <link>https://www.barcampcork.org/2006/09/20/blacknight-are-our-latest-sponsors/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2006 13:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.barcampcork.org/2006/09/20/blacknight-are-our-latest-sponsors/</guid>
      <description>Michele over at Irish web-host provider Blacknight has kindly offered to sponsor some of the after-event celebrations. Now we just need to figure out what those celebrations are. Thanks Michele. We really are getting a lovely mix of sponsors now.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Talk Talk</title>
      <link>https://www.barcampcork.org/2006/09/20/talk-talk/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2006 09:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.barcampcork.org/2006/09/20/talk-talk/</guid>
      <description>We’re playing with some options for online chat during the event. IRC is the most obvious one but we need to make sure that we have a web interface to that for those who don’t have an IRC client installed. One neat little doodah we found is Lace which is a nice web-based mini-chatroom. The author</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We need your e-mail addresses</title>
      <link>https://www.barcampcork.org/2006/09/20/we-need-your-e-mail-addresses/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2006 09:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.barcampcork.org/2006/09/20/we-need-your-e-mail-addresses/</guid>
      <description>One thing which we have avoided on the wiki is asking for your e-mail addresses. This is both for privacy and to stop scumbag spammers harvesting them. However, to take part in the backnetwork, we will need to send you an activation code. If you wish to take part (and we recommend you do), please send</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Madgex provides BarCampIreland with a backnetwork</title>
      <link>https://www.barcampcork.org/2006/09/19/madgex-provides-barcampireland-with-a-backnetwork/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2006 17:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.barcampcork.org/2006/09/19/madgex-provides-barcampireland-with-a-backnetwork/</guid>
      <description>This really is the icing on the cake for the event. Madgex, a web development company based in Brighton, are providing a full backnetwork for BarCampIreland. Have a look at the one they did for the d.Construct 2006 conference recently. Just to list some of the features:
Every attendee gets a profile page You can indicate your</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fear of Flying</title>
      <link>https://www.barcampcork.org/2006/09/19/fear-of-flying/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2006 09:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.barcampcork.org/2006/09/19/fear-of-flying/</guid>
      <description>Elly has signed up to talk about getting non-technical people using web technologies. This is something I obsess about a lot. We got my Dad from technophobe to e-mail to SMS to RyanAir.com in five short(!) years. Hell he googled for someone yesterday. There is still a long way to go but I’m one of</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Check out the pimped-up logos!</title>
      <link>https://www.barcampcork.org/2006/09/18/check-out-the-pimped-up-logos/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2006 15:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.barcampcork.org/2006/09/18/check-out-the-pimped-up-logos/</guid>
      <description>We updated the logos on this blog and on the Wiki with the design that is going on the t-shirts. A big thanks again to Ed and Tomasz in Hosting365 for sorting these out for us. Definitely the best variation on the core BarCamp logo I’ve seen so far.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tell us all about yourself</title>
      <link>https://www.barcampcork.org/2006/09/18/tell-us-all-about-yourself/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2006 12:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.barcampcork.org/2006/09/18/tell-us-all-about-yourself/</guid>
      <description>I’ve just put a Profiles page up on the Wiki. The idea is to provide a very short outline of your background so that people can discover those of similar interests and perhaps come up with some new ideas for presentations that they can give or would like to hear. I saw a joint presentation</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Another excellent sponsor</title>
      <link>https://www.barcampcork.org/2006/09/18/another-excellent-sponsor/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2006 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.barcampcork.org/2006/09/18/another-excellent-sponsor/</guid>
      <description>We’re delighted to announce that Sigmar Recruitment have decided to sponsor BarCampIreland. Thanks! Every sponsor we get is a great validation of the value of the event. There is now a very strong desire to make this the first of many BarCamps around the country.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fantastic idea for a session</title>
      <link>https://www.barcampcork.org/2006/09/17/fantastic-idea-for-a-session/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2006 20:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.barcampcork.org/2006/09/17/fantastic-idea-for-a-session/</guid>
      <description>Emmet has come up with an awesome idea for some of the sessions at BarCampIreland. He has mentioned it here and over at the Wiki and is looking for people to sign-up. The concept is called Petcha Kucha (or Klaatu Barada Nikto as I keep saying) and the basic idea is that each speaker presents 20</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>And in the equally long tradition of the hours after an event</title>
      <link>https://www.barcampcork.org/2006/09/15/and-in-the-equally-long-tradition-of-the-hours-after-an-event/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2006 10:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.barcampcork.org/2006/09/15/and-in-the-equally-long-tradition-of-the-hours-after-an-event/</guid>
      <description>Adam wonders if we should have BeerCamp afterwards. We’ve some ideas there but shout out your suggestions for what and where. For the utterly confused the overall BarCamp blog itself points out that it is “bar” as in foo not Bar as in Beer. I think we should do a quick test at the door to</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>In the long tradition of the night before</title>
      <link>https://www.barcampcork.org/2006/09/14/in-the-long-tradition-of-the-night-before/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2006 13:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.barcampcork.org/2006/09/14/in-the-long-tradition-of-the-night-before/</guid>
      <description>Joe Drumgoole wonders if anyone is around on the Friday night before the BarCamp starts. Damien, Walter and I will be in town getting the place set up so I think he can count on all of us being up for something. Walter has suggested Wagamama to start with and I second that since I’ve been</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to monitor the blog buzz on BarCampIreland</title>
      <link>https://www.barcampcork.org/2006/09/13/how-to-monitor-the-blog-buzz-on-barcampireland/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2006 14:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.barcampcork.org/2006/09/13/how-to-monitor-the-blog-buzz-on-barcampireland/</guid>
      <description>First off, if you do blog about the event, please please add BarCampIreland as a Technorati tag. Then as Walter pointed out to me, anyone can subscribe to the RSS feed for that term or you can just keep an eye on this page over at Technorati to catch all the buzz in one place.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>T-shirts coming along nicely</title>
      <link>https://www.barcampcork.org/2006/09/13/t-shirts-coming-along-nicely/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2006 06:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.barcampcork.org/2006/09/13/t-shirts-coming-along-nicely/</guid>
      <description>We are deeply grateful for all sponsorship of the event but we’d particularly like to highlight the work being done by Ed Byrne and Tomasz of hosting365. They have been unreasonably patient with us as we tried to figure out exactly what logo we wanted. Tomasz put together a bunch of great options in double</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>More sponsors</title>
      <link>https://www.barcampcork.org/2006/09/12/more-sponsors/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2006 08:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.barcampcork.org/2006/09/12/more-sponsors/</guid>
      <description>Trinity Venture Capital have kindly given us sponsorship and will be speaking at the event too. We’re guessing a talk entitled “Understanding and accessing venture capital funding” is going to be ever so slightly popular.
We hopefully be announcing another sponsor or two over the next couple of days.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sponsors</title>
      <link>https://www.barcampcork.org/2006/09/10/sponsors/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Sep 2006 09:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.barcampcork.org/2006/09/10/sponsors/</guid>
      <description>We’d like to thank all of our confirmed sponsors so far:
 Webworks (and Enterprise Ireland) for the great building and free WiFi Heineken Ireland Qumas Roam4Free Bubble Brothers Hosting365  If you wish to sponsor the event in any way please contact Conor O’Neill, Walter Higgins or Damien Mulley.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Official Press Release</title>
      <link>https://www.barcampcork.org/2006/09/07/official-press-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2006 10:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.barcampcork.org/2006/09/07/official-press-release/</guid>
      <description>Irish IT Conference turns the audience into the presenters.
The first BarCamp event to be held in Ireland will bring a fresh twist to the usual IT gatherings. BarCamp is an event model imported from the United States with the mantra of No spectators, only participants.
Conor O&amp;rsquo;Neill, of Argolon Solutions, one of the event organisers stated BarCamp is an informal gathering of people from technical and business backgrounds who wish to share their knowledge and learn from others.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
